Hi girls, this is Janet Fiscuito and I will be your burlesque teacher.
What actually burlesque is, burlesque is the art of these bar excellence and I
'm sure that
all of you know Dita Bontis, she's the best, she's really the queen.
Everyone would like to learn burlesque.
Why? Because burlesque is definitely useful to give more power to your femin
inity and
to know better your body.
What what means like knowing better your body.
It's I think for us performer it's quite essential to know how to move our body
, what
to move and why and above all the feeling we we have while we perform or why we
we bring
this thing on stage, let's say it's because we have this artistic emergency or
we have
a feeling there is like a message we want to bring outside our body.
The burlesque is really a complete art.
It's a place a free place where everyone can be what they want or they can just
extend
or amplify what they feel or what they want to turn into.
I actually built up my career because I always dreamed to be and to work in a
circus like
in the early 30s, 20s so that was my dream and in my burlesque shows for
example I bring
my vision and my dreams on stage and what I want and what and what's my desire
is to
guide my audience inside my visions and my dreams.
So it's a sort of imaginary that I build up also with my tattoos so the idea is
that
I'm the doctor from the era and everybody comes to see me like of course like
performing
as a as a trapeze artist, since I'm a trapeze artist, he's a fire eater.
I like to manipulate the fire as well to juggle with the fire.
So basically that's my idea and in all my shows this is what I bring on stage.
So every character is inspired by some figure, some character inside the old
vintage circus.
So actually what would you like to be?
Let's work on this together in this next course that we're going to start.
We're going to learn more or less basics for example that we can bring all
around eras.
So if you prefer to be like the 20s cute charleston flapper girl or you want to
be like a 50s,
60s vega sugar, there's a lot of opportunities.
So first of all let's learn the basics like the shimmy shake, the art of teeth.
And then we can create our character.
I will also help you and give you advices on costumes, creations, on makeup and
many
other things on request.
So don't be shy, I wish you're not.
Enjoy, join us, join me in this for less course.
I can wait to know you, ciao!